I am always friends, you are very welcome to our YouTube channel,
friends, in today's
video we will talk about ICICI
Prudential Life Insurance jobs,
so let me tell you that for the last
two-four days, we were getting a lot of comments from you guys,
tell us about this like inspiration job, friends,
how do you get an account here and
what is the job profile, the interview is famous,
training and how many days it lasts,
how much is the salary per day, okay, that was done
by some people, so we will
tell you the complete details about it in this video, so you should
subscribe to our channel right now
so that whatever chop notifications come in future, first of all,
in our channel you will get daily banking job related
information, apart from this, friends, you will keep getting private
job related information and phone homework, okay,
those other unknown things that you get or you will keep getting,
now let's talk
here about the potential of staff, so
whatever question you asked here,
I will repeat it once again, today
you had asked that how difficult is the second interview
process,
what can be asked in the pimp interview,
okay  This was asked after that
how long is the attending product and
how much salary is received, the main
topic yesterday was how is ICICI Prudential
Life Insurance job, should one do it
or not, so in this video you have to
talk about it, before this
I will tell you an example that
in childhood and like we used to go to school in the beginning, from
first class, then what used to happen there,
like if we come and talk about our childhood in first class, then for the
first one
week, two weeks or one month
we used to enjoy going to school a lot, or if there are
small children who are mixing New Year
in school, then they like going to school for one month,
after that one and a half
what happens is that they pretend not to go to school, they
don't go to school, okay, if
they don't go to school then they get beaten by their mother,
if they go to school then they get
beaten by the ma'am or the teachers, whoever it is, it is said that
because they don't do their homework or do
n't do their homework properly, because of this
they get beaten there, okay  If
he doesn't go, he stays at home,
but he will have to go to school, so
friends, some situations like this happen in life,
explain about it in detail,
subscribe in detail, okay, then you should
subscribe completely,
if you want to do a job there, then
after that you will be able to do it
because you people specifically asked whether you should
subscribe, then I will
tell you about it, the subscribe is
away, my option is
here, I will tell you about the Yagya and
friends, whatever a little space people have
shared with people, I will
tell you about that, so friends, it happens here that
if
you want to join this, okay, then
you may face some problem,
I want to tell you what it is, or there
is an Additional Secretary, you have a
number one company in India, okay, working here,
you get a good salary,
along with that, you have this report company,
okay, so friends, you should work here,
according to me you should work,
but many people believe that you should
not work in this life insurance  I know why I say this
because look at any side
there is a lot of pressure
and you get worried and pressure happens
when you don't do the work properly, then the pressure that
you have is going to come,
okay, one more thing here is that you should start working
from my home, I am saying this
because if you take any life
insurance field and
talk about such open sewing prince, then
here the salary is also very good,
yes you will get that pressure anywhere else,
but first you should keep yourself a little focused on it for one, two, three minutes,
after that you will start taking the
market knowledge of this frill,
okay, then after that it will be
very easy for you to do this job and you will
get size, as far as I have seen,
in this film, he has been tied to the same company for 15-20 years and is
still working, okay
and in fact, this guy is also my friend for 5 years,
and if we talk friends,
then what kind of comments did
these people have in the beginning, I love you all
Question and shake here,
never tell too much about job hunting, then only you have gained
knowledge of the third market and
now you have gone and done it well in the market,
okay this is it and according to me
you should do it, if you should not do it then
I have told you what you should not do, if not then you should do it,
see you like
Sharmila Tagore but your sense of communication is
not good then you can easily pony up like this
race, in any life you can do whatever you want
there, it is
very important to have communication skills in this field, okay, only then you
can do this celery well, so this is the
second topic, friends,
see what is the interview process here and when you
come for the interview,
you will come to know in the first round itself that
you are not going to be the one because the
peers and the personal surroundings there, the
interviewer will
ask questions about you, okay, he will find out
how much extra your communication is to that extent  Whether
you have knowledge about the product or not, it
is fine at that very second, when you will make the termination from there, then
how are your eyes, fine, and
how are you able to answer the question and your
previous behavior can be checked there, then they
ask you one or two questions about sales, generally,
after the pen or laptop, whoever we are will
ask you to seal it and tell us, then he will
wait at your house and fry something, then you
can answer about that,
like I have some right person, so now do not
even go for the interview, friends, there
two-three Rahul's interviews take place and it is also
different there, mostly I have
seen that you get selected in a single day, they
also
provide the letter in a single day, it is a
good thing to provide everything in a single day,
I understand ours on time,
their time is also saved, so these are
two-three interviews, that is done
and more, the second one is here
today  Some time they ask you how many days you
can take to launch it, then you say that
you will not take more than two days here,
after that you will join, after joining, there will be more
training of about 15 to 20 days
and during this time you have to acquire
knowledge about whatever is upsetting for the department and whoever comes to attend here
and there, you will get it,
but whatever doubts you have, it is
important for you to tell them, clearing the doubts will
not be possible if you come to Jodi Akbar floor, so
after 15 to 20 days, after getting selected,
as you come, your
Excel work starts there, but friends,
here you are
not given any pressure for 15-1 month, everything,
after that, your work gets a little one and a half, if we are
not able to do it better than this, then it is necessary to put pressure on you there,
this is what happens in the company,
okay, and this is done friends, you will be
able to do the work comfortably, if you are interested in it, then  If we
talk
about turmeric, how much salary do you get here, as far as
such time pass, then
friends, here there is one type of salary which is around 30,
which you and Saif can get, that is
2,000 rupees per year, if you have an exchange,
okay, then the salary you can get there also, you can get it on
roti, you
can get it from MP, if you
have any course in sales and relationship management,
or you have
done RSS marketing course from them here,
or apart from this, you have done
any course on banking service, then your salary here is
going up, as you might have seen
before, whether it is any program of accident
or the pure program of ICC Bank,
or any message send a
ship management program of Anti, you should do
their PET, if you drop
knife on it in marriage, then it is a PET
course of one year,
its course fee is around three and a half lakh rupees, and there is job
guarantee and a good position at level one,
level two, level three, which is
handed over to it.  They provide 45 lakh rupees annually Urs
happens here, okay if there are some courses of that kind for
people then everyone and
you get increased here, let's talk about everything friends
this is done related to this topic if
I forgot to say something then you can add it in the comment box that you want to
know about it then I will replace it for you by commenting
and apart from this
I have given the feeling by maximizing Facebook and WhatsApp
whichever you can follow below
Sarthak Amla function job is never prohibited in gender
check it out there
and this is next9news answer that if
you want to see about this company then definitely
tell me by commenting so then friends this